New York State Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors; Records apap315
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Chronological Files, 1995-2005; Undated; 2; 12.0 cu. ft.
  - January, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 1)
  - February, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 2)
  - March, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 3)
  - April, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 4-5)
  - May, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 6-7)
  - June, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 8-9)
  - July, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 10-11)
  - August, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 12)
  - September, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 13-14)
  - October, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 15)
  - November, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 16)
  - December, 2005 (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 17-18)
  - General CLMHD information, Undated (Box 12 (2-Chronological Files), Folder 19)
- Office of Legislative and Government Affairs Director, 1991-2003; Undated; 3; 3.0 cu. ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains information related to state reinvestment plans, Medicaid concerns, managed care, and housing. While materials on all of these topics also can be found in Series 5, 6, and 7, the documents in this series were all kept specifically by the director of legislative and government affairs and therefore remain together in their own series.
  - 1998 Reinvestment extender, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 1)
  - Community Mental Health Reinvestment Bill letters sent to other organizations requesting support from D. Coughlin, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 2)
  - Community Mental Health Reinvestment Bill press clips, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 3)
  - Community Mental Health Reinvestment Bill press clips, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 4)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill of 1992 #2 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 5)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill of 1992 #3- with lines and brackets, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 6)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill of 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 7-8)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill of 1993- Comments, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 9)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill testimony, 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 10-11)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill: Language amendments, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 12)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill: Language amendments, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 13)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill: Legislation (Drafts), 1991-1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 14-15)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill: Legislation (Drafts), 1992; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 16)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Bill: Local Medicaid share, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 17)
  - Community Mental Health Resources Trust Fund, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 18)
  - Community Reinvestment Funding 1994-1995, 1994 August 08 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 19)
  - County mental health Medicaid expenditures (county responses), 1997 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 20)
  - County mental hygiene expenditures, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 21)
  - Developmental Disabilities Services Office feedback, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 22)
  - Grants, 1994; Undated (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 23)
  - List of support for community mental health resources bill, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 24)
  - Managed care, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 25)
  - Managed care, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 26)
  - Managed care demos under NYSDSS, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 27)
  - Mandate Relief Project, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 1)
  - Medicaid budget bill- Health only, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 2)
  - Medicaid managed care- Articles and reports, 1989-1991 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 3)
  - Medicaid managed care- Articles and reports, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 4)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Coalition, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 5)
  - Medicaid managed care- Coalition for Homeless and New York Public Welfare Association, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 6)
  - Members/background, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 7)
  - Membership meetings, NYSCLMHD, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 8)
  - Mental health terms and background, 1989 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 9)
  - New and expanded programs funded through reinvestment 1994-1995 through 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 10)
  - New York City- Managed special care, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 11)
  - Office of Mental Health 1999 contract agreement and TAP, 1997-2000 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 12)
  - Office of Mental Health 1999 contract agreement and TAP, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 13)
  - Office of Mental Health 551 regulations, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 14)
  - Office of Mental Health 551 regulations, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 15)
  - Office of Mental Health: Revisions to Part 592 Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 16)
  - Office of Mental Health: Reinvestment planning guidelines, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 17-18)
  - Office of Mental Health: Reinvestment reference charts, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 19)
  - Partnership Committee, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 20)
  - Proposed new Part 551 comments and prior arrival review issues, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 21)
  - Proposed revisions to Part 592- Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 22)
  - Redeployment of mental health resources for the 21st century, 1997 December-1998 January (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 23)
  - Reinvestment- General, 1993-1995; 1997 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 24)
  - Reinvestment- General, 1993-1998 (Box 2 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 25)
  - Reinvestment Group (The One Bill Group), 1993-1994 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 1)
  - Reinvestment guidelines, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 2)
  - Reinvestment guidelines, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 3)
  - Reinvestment guidelines, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 4)
  - Reinvestment implementation, 1992-1995 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 5)
  - Reinvestment implementation, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 6)
  - Reinvestment implementation- Acts to amend state finance and mental hygiene laws, 1992 October 19; 1993 November 01; Undated (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 7)
  - Reinvestment- Legislation and correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 8)
  - Reinvestment- letter-writing campaign, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 9)
  - Reinvestment- Memos of support, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 10)
  - Reinvestment overview, 1993; 1995 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 11)
  - Reinvestment resolutions, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 12)
  - Special Needs Plans, 1997-2000 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 13-14)
  - Special Needs Plans (information and data), 1997-1998; Undated (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 15)
  - Special Needs Plans (information and data), 1998 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 16)
  - Survey- Reinvestment evaluation, 1997 April (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 17)
  - TAP Day, Rensselaerville Institute, September 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 18)
  - Welfare reform- Act to amend social services law, 1996 December 02 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 19-20)
  - Welfare reform- "Putting the Pieces Together" by Senator M.L. Rath and act to amend education law, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (3-Office of Legislative and Government Affairs ), Folder 21)
- County Plans, Operations, and Government, 1980-2009; Undated; 4; 4.2 cu. ft.
  These records are specific to the counties of New York as they participated in coordinated care efforts for people with mental health needs. There are documents regarding activities unique to certain counties, such as closures of facilities and resignations of Conference members. There are also letters, memos, and reports covering topics like mandate relief recommendations, comprehensive outpatient programs, health needs surveys, and funding issues.
  - 135th Anniversary celebration of the Schuyler Center, 2006 November 16 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 1)
  - Albany County, 1992-1997 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 2)
  - Albany County letter to Mental Health Commissioners, 2007 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 3)
  - Amendment of 14NYCRR Parts 587 and 588- Comprehensive mandate relief, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 4)
  - Broome County, 1991; 1993-1994; 1997 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 5)
  - Broome County- Annual report, 1990 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 6)
  - Broome County- Annual report, 1992 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 7)
  - By-laws and amendments, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 8)
  - By-laws amendments ballots, 1994 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 9)
  - Cayuga County, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 10)
  - Chautauqua County, 1991 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 11)
  - Chemung County, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 12)
  - Clinton County, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 13)
  - Columbia County, 1990; 1995 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 14)
  - Community of practice for local partners, 2009; Undated (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 15)
  - Consolidated budget reporting manual and forms, 1994 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 16)
  - Cortland County, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 17)
  - County plans A-F, 2006 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 18)
  - County plans F-H, 2006 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 19)
  - County plans J-O, 2006 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 20)
  - County plans O-S, 2006 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 21)
  - County plans S-W, 2006 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 22)
  - County responses- Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1991; 1995; 1997 (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 23)
  - County responses- Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 24)
  - County testimony on Office of Mental Retardation and Developmentally Disabled regulation review, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 1-3)
  - Delaware County, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 4)
  - Delaware County, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 5)
  - Department of Mental Hygiene property utilization book, Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 6)
  - Dictionary of Mental Health Terms, 1989; 1998 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 7)
  - Directors of community service, 1989; 1994; 1997 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 8)
  - Dutchess County, 1991-1994; 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 9)
  - Erie County, 1991-1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 10)
  - Erie County, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 11)
  - Essex County, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 12)
  - Fingerlakes region, 1994 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 13)
  - Forms of county government, 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 14)
  - Franklin County, 1990; 1993 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 15)
  - Fulton County, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 16)
  - Genesee County, 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 17)
  - Guidelines reinvestment plan for 1995, 1994 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 18)
  - Jefferson County, 1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 19)
  - Lewis County, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 20)
  - Livingston County, 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 21)
  - Local area plan guidelines for 1995, 1994 April (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 22)
  - "Local Government and Managed Governance", Presented at Managed Care and Managed Change Conference, 1996 June (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 23)
  - Local Services Plan for Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- County guidance, 1995 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 24)
  - Madison County, 1993 (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 25)
  - Mandate relief recommendations, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 26)
  - Mandate relief recommendations, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 27)
  - Mandate relief recommendations, 1995 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 1)
  - Manuals: "Mental Health Care in America" and "Community Health Needs Assessment in a Managed Care Environment", 1995; 2001 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 2)
  - Mental hygiene law, Title E, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 3)
  - Mission statement, 1994 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 4)
  - Monroe County, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 5)
  - Montgomery County, 1992-1993; 1997 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 6)
  - Nassau County, 1992-1994; 1996 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 7)
  - Nassau County, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 8)
  - New York City, 1991; 1994 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 9)
  - New York City, 1994-1996 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 10)
  - New York City: "Deinstitutionalization- An Epilogue", 1985 December 03 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 11)
  - Niagara County, 1991; 1993 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 12)
  - North Country directors, 1991 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 13)
  - NYS Department of Mental Hygiene Consolidated Fiscal Reporting Manual (Agency administration expenses), 1988 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 14)
  - NYS Department of Mental Hygiene Consolidated Fiscal Reporting Manual (DAAA program definitions and code numbers), 1988; Undated (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 15)
  - NYS Office Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- County planning data supplements, 1996 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 16)
  - NYS Office of Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- Local services plan guidelines, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 17)
  - NYSCLMHD Annual Report, 2006 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 18)
  - NYSCLMHD Annual Report, 2007 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 19)
  - NYSCLMHD strategic framework, 1994 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 20)
  - Office of Mental Health-Comprehensive Outpatient Programs, 1991 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 21)
  - Office of Regulatory and Management Assistance Taskforce on CFR Reform final report, 1994 March (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 22)
  - Oneida County, 1980; 1991; 1995 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 23)
  - Onondaga County, 1990-1994 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 24)
  - Ontario County, 1992 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 25)
  - Orange County, 1990-1994 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 26)
  - Planning guidelines for counties and boroughs, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 27)
  - Prepaid mental health plan: Office of Mental Health, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 28)
  - Prepaid mental health plan: Office of Mental Health, 1996 (Box 3 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 29)
  - Prepaid mental health plan: Office of Mental Health, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 1)
  - Prospectivity- Comprehensive Outpatient Programs, 1993 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 2)
  - Putnam County, 1991 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 3)
  - Regulation review process by county, 1995 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, 1991-1994 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County: "Addressing the needs of Incarcerated Women with Concurring Disorders: One Program's Response"- Summer 1998 Issue of Jail Suicide/Mental Health Update with accompanying letter, 1998 June; 1996 June (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 6)
  - Resignation letter of Lloyd Sederer, 2007 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 7)
  - Rockland County, 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 8)
  - Saratoga County, 1993; Undated (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 9)
  - Schenectady County, 1991-1994 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County, 1993-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 11)
  - Schoharie County, 1991; 1993 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 12)
  - Schuyler County, 1991-1992; 1994 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 13)
  - Schuyler County mental health plan, 1995 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 14)
  - Schuyler County mental retardation/developmental disabilities plan, 1995 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 15)
  - Schuyler County substance abuse plan, 1995 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 16)
  - Seneca County, 1992 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 17)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1991-1993 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 18)
  - Statewide directory, 1996 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 19)
  - Steuben County, 1992 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 20)
  - Suffolk County, 1991-1994 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 21)
  - Sullivan County, 1991; 1993; 1997 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 22)
  - Survey on the NYS public mental health system, 1988 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 23)
  - Tioga County, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 24)
  - Tioga County, 1991-1992 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 25)
  - Tioga County, 1991-1994 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 26)
  - Tioga County, 1994-1997 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 27)
  - Ulster County, 1991-1993; 1995 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 28)
  - Warren/Washington County, 1991-1992; 1995 (Box 4 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 29)
  - Wayne County, 1992 (Box 5 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 1)
  - Westchester County, 1992-1995 (Box 5 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 2)
  - Western region, Undated (Box 5 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 3)
  - Western Regional county directors, 1993 (Box 5 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 4)
  - Wyoming County, 1991; 1993 (Box 5 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 5)
  - Yates County, 1992 (Box 5 (4-County Plans, Operations, and Governme), Folder 6)
- Projects and Committees, 1979-2001; Undated; 5; 5.0 cu. ft.
  This series focuses on some of the Conference’s more specific endeavors, including (but not limited to) those with definitive start and end dates as opposed to ongoing tasks. Examples include the Kids Oneida project, the Commission on the 21st Century, various grant applications, and the committees for developmental disabilities and chemical dependency.
  - Center for Behavioral Health Institute (CBHI), 1997-1999 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 1)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 2)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Managed care joint meeting minutes, 1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 3)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1994 October-1995 June (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 4)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1995 October (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 5)